Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1949-2010
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 1: Administrative records, 1949-2007 (Boxes 1-196)
  - Subseries 1.3: Financial papers/personnel records, 1950-2000
    - Sub-subseries 1.3.1: Financial papers, 1950-2000
      - Royalties, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Royalties, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Royalties, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Royalties, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Royalties, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Royalties, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Royalties, 1983-1984 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Royalties, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Royalties, 1985-1986 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Royalties, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Royalties Information, 1997-1998 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Royalties, Undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Royalties - Abyssinia, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Royalties - American Buffalo, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Royalties - American Splendor, Undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Royalties Income - Anarchist, 1983-1984 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Royalties - Animal Cracker Extension, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Royalties - Avner/Eccentric, Undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Royalties - Banjo Dancing, 1981-1987 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Royalties - Banjo Dancing, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Royalties - Banjo Dancing, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Royalties - Banjo Dancing, 1982-1983 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Royalties - Banjo Dancing, 1983-1984 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Royalties - Banjo Dancing Payments, 1984-195 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Royalties - Banjo Dancing Payments, 1985-186 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Royalties - Banjo Dancing Payments, 1986-1987 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Royalties - Banjo Dancing, 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - Royalties - Banjo Dancing, 1988-189 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Royalties - Beehive, 1986-1987 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - Royalties - Before it Hits Home, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - Royalties - Bette and Boo, 1986-1987 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - Royalties - Billy Bishop, 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Royalties - Born Guilty, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Royalties - Briar Patch, 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - The Caucasian Chalk Circle, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Royalties - Cerceau, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Royalties - Checkmates, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Royalties - Cherry Orchard, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Royalties - A Chorus of Disapproval, 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Royalties - A Circle in the Square, Box Office statements - "Loose Ends Royalties", 1979-1982 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Royalties - A Circle in the Square, Box Office statements - "Loose Ends Royalties", 1979 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Royalties - Close Than Ever, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Royalties - Cocoanuts, 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Royalties - Conquest of the South Pole, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Royalties - Crime and Punishment, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Royalties - The Crucible, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Royalties - A Doll House, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Royalties - Emigres, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Royalties - Emlyn Williams, 1975-1977 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Royalties - Enrico IV, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Royalties - Execution 84-85, 1988-1989 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Royalties - Fences, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Royalties - The Fool Show, 1988-1989 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Royalties - Foolsfire Royalties info, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Royalties - Foursome, Royalties Payment, September 1973 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Royalties - From the Mississippi Delta, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Royalties - Gertrude Stein, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Royalties - Gertrude Stein, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Royalties - The Glass Menagerie, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Royalties - Glengarry/Glenn Ross, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - Royalties - Heart Break House, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Royalties - Horatio, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - Royalties - The Immigrant, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 19)
      - Royalties - Joe Turner, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - Royalties - Judevine, April 1989 (Box 54, Folder 21)
      - Royalties - Juno and the Paycock, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 22)
      - Royalties - K2 NYC, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 23)
      - Royalties - K2 Ext '82 Running Costs, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 24)
      - Royalties - Karamazov Brothers, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 25)
      - Royalties - Karamazov Brothers, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 26)
      - Royalties - Karamazov Brothers, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 27)
      - Royalties - Karamazov Brothers, 1982-1983 (Box 54, Folder 28)
      - Royalties - Karamazov Brothers, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 29)
      - Royalties - Kings Men, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 30)
      - Royalties - Les Blancs, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Royalties - A Lie of the Mind, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Royalties - Light Up the Sky, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Royalties - The Man Who Came to Dinner, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Royalties - Merrily We Roll Along, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Royalties - A Midsummer's Night's Dream, Undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Royalties - Moon Children, March, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Royalties - Monteith and Rand, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Royalties - Mummenschanz, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Royalties - My Children! My Africa!, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Royalties - Nightclub Cantata, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Royalties - Nothing Sacred, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Royalties - On the Town, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Royalties - On the Way Home, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Royalties - On the Way Home (FY90), 1990 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Royalties - On the Way Home (FY91), 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Royalties - One Mo' Time, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Royalties - One Mo' Time, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Royalties - Our Town, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Royalties - Ourselves Alone, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - Royalties - Ourselves Alone, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - Royalties - Piggy Bank Royalties (Pots of Money), 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 22)
      - Royalties - Playboy of the West Indies, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 23)
      - Royalties - Play Labs, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 24)
      - Royalties - Pygmalion, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Royalties - Radio Hour, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Royalties - Raisin, 1972-1973 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Royalties - Raisin, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Royalties - Regard of Flight, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Royalties - Ring Round the Moon, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Royalties - Rivers/Ravines, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Royalties - Rosewater Extension, Undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Royalties - The Seagull, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Royalties - She Stoops to Conquer, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Royalties - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Royalties - Stand-up Tragedy, 1989-1990 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Royalties - Suzuki, 1987-1989 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Royalties - Teibele, 1979-1981 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Royalties - Tintypes, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Royalties - Tintypes Newwald, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Royalties - Tomfoolery, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Royalties - Tomfoolery Ext, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Royalties - Two Gentlemen of Verona, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Royalties - Victor Borge, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - Royalties - Vivisections from the Blown Mind, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Royalties - A Walk in the Woods, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Royalties - Workshop Royalties, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Salary Survey, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Salary Survey Returns, Undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Sale of Arena Stage from Arena Enterprises, Inc to Washington Drama Society, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Sample Acknowledgements, 1988-1989 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Mark Sandground, April 20, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Saturn/Columbia Books, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Dr. Robert Schattner, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Swartz, Stuart, circa 1980s (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Season Surveys for Lila Wallace/Ames, 1992-1994 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Herschel Shesteck, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Shubert Foundation, 1973-1978 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Shubert Foundation Report Fiscal, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Shubert Foundation Financial Information, 1976-1978 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Shubert, 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Shubert, 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Shubert, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Shubert, 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Shubert, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Shubert, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Shubert, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - Paula Robin Silvert, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - Albert Small, 1984-1986 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - Southwest Project, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 23)
      - Southwest Project, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Southwest Project, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Stabilization II - 2nd Draft, October 26, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Stabilization II - 2nd Draft, October 26, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Stage II Stock Sales, circa 1960s (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Stock/Shareholder Information and Development Mailings, 1950-1980s (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Walter John Stassel, Sr., December 15-16, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Hon. Potter Stewart, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Stockholders - Present and Potential, 1956, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Stone, Richard Bernard, 1985-1987 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Stoppard, Tom, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Strong Foundation Grant - $10,000, 1974-1975 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Subscriptions - Mailings - Schedules, 1982-1983 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Subscription - '81 Budget Calendar, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Subscriptions, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Subscriptions - Renewal Invoice, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Subscription Newsletter, Undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Subscription Brochure Copy, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Subscriptions Brochure Copy, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Subscription Calendar, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Subscription Campaign, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Subscription - Minor Printer Materials, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Subscriptions - Phone Sales, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Subscription - Print Ads, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Subscriptions - Printing Bids, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Subscription - Renewal Forms, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Subscription - Washingtonian, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Subscription Plan, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Subsidiary Rights Project, 1990-1995 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Sherwood Tarlow, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - A. Alfred Taubman (see also Woodrow and Lothrop), 1984-1986 (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - Taylor, Charles, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - Telemarketing, 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 20)
      - Theatre Development Publications, 1947-1953 (Box 59, Folder 21)
      - Theatrical Law and Child Labor Inspections, 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - The Trammell Crow Company, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - The Trammell Crow Company, 1985 - 1986 (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - Trust Indenture, January 2, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - Trustee Training, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Underwriter's Support, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - United Arts Fund, 1974-1975, 1977-1978 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - United Way, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - U.S. Steel Foundation, '72-73, '74-75, '75-76, 1972-1976 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Van American Foundation - Grants - Financial, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Helen Ver Slandig (Madame Wellington), August 1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Wallace Funds, 1995-1996 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Washington Drama Society, circa 1950s (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Washington Drama Society, Inc - List of Bondholders for payment of interest, September 1, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Washington Drama Society, Inc - List of Bondholders for payment of interest, September 1, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - WDS Bond Insurance, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - WDS Bond Insurance, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - WDS Bond Insurance, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - WDS Bond Insurance, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - WDS Bond Insurance, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - WDS Bond Insurance, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Charles Cafritz Wilkes, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Young, William, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Wilson, Kendall W., 1984 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - WNET-Exxon, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Workshop Grant Summer Request, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Workshop Materials, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Sub-subseries 1.3.2: Personnel/staff, 1951-1997
      Sub-subseries 1.3.2: Sub-subseries 2: Personnel records includes information on staff at Arena Stage, as well as correspondence with actors who were offered Arena roles.
      Some records in sub-subseries 3 (Personnel/staff) contain personal identification information, such as social security numbers. Folders in this sub-subseries must be screened by an archivist before being given to researchers.
      - Actor Biography M-R, 1954-1969 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Actor Biography S-T, 1952-1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Actor Biography T-Z, 1956-1969 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Actress Biography A-B, 1954-1969 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Actress Biography C-F, 1956-1969 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Actress Biography G-I, 1955-1969 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Actress Biography J-L, 1960-1969 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Actress Biography M-O, 1954-1969 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Actress Biography P-R, 1955-1969 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Actress Biography S-Z, 1967-1969 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - A I, 1973-1988 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - B I, 1957-1991 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - B II (1 of 2), 1980-1990 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - B II (2 of 2), 1954-1984 (Box 64, Folder 4)
        Contains a letter from Annette Bening.
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - C I, 1952-1988 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - C II, 1956-1983 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - C II, 1965-1990 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - D I, 1958-1991 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - D II, 1959-1981 (Box 64, Folder 9)
        Contains headshots and a letter from Olympia Dukakis.
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - E I, 1975-1979 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - F I, 1960-1984 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - F II, 1957-1987 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - G I, 1955-1981 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - G II, 1965-1985 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - G II, 1965-1989 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - H I, 1959-1988 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - H II, 1957-1989 (Box 65, Folder 4)
        Contains a letter from Rosemary Harris.
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - I, J I, 1959-1991 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - IJ - II, 1965-1990 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - K I, 1957-1990 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - K II, 1965-1990 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - L I, 1966-1980 (Box 65, Folder 9)
        Contains letters, headshots, and a CV from John Lithgow.
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - L II, 1957-1990 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - M I, 1959-1991 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - M II, 1954-1980 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name- M II, 1959-1990 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - N, O I, 1951-1980 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - P, Q I, 1959-1989 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - P, Q II, 1951-1990 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - R I, 1953-1990 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - R II, 1956-1980s (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - S I, 1963-1991 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - S II, 1963-1991 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - T I, 1962-1989 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - T II, 1954-1982 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - U, V II, 1973-1991 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - W I, 1972-1989 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - W II, 1956-1981 (Box 67, Folder 5)
        Contains letters from Sigourney Weaver.
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - Y, Z I, 1962-1980 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Alphabetical Subject/Name - X, Y, Z II, 1980-1981 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Jane Alexander, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Arliss, Dimitra, 1971-1972 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Alan Ayckbourn, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Guy Bergquist, circa 1990s (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Biographic Actors A-C, list of actors with biographies, 1958-1998 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Biographic Actors A-C, 1957-1969 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Biographic Actors A-C, 1954-1969 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Biographic Actors D-F, 1955-1969 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Biographic Actors D-F, 1950s-1960s (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Biographic Actors F-H, 1965-1968 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Biographic Actors I-L, 1950s-1960s (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Biographic Actors G-L, 1957-1969 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Biographic Actors M, 1950s-1960s (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Biographic Actors N-O, 1950s-1960s (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Biographic Actors P-R, 1950s-1960s (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Biographic Actors S-Z, 1950s-1960s (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Biographic Actresses A-C, 1950s-1960s (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Biographic Actresses D-F, 1950s-1960s (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Biographic Actresses G-K, 1950s-1960s (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Biographic Actresses K-M, 1950s-1960s (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Biographic Actresses N-R, 1950s-1960s (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Biographic Actresses S-Z, 1950s-1960s (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Biography Material - Staff, circa 1960s (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Borucezov, Radu/Mirunia, Pintelle, Lucian - Immigration Materials, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Carrasquillo, Jose, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Chang, Wei-Wen - Immigration Materials, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Child Actors - On the Razzle, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Contact Sheets, 1970s (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Damood, Ahmad - Immigration Materials, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Dougherty, Jeannie, circa 1970 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Dowling, Joe - Immigration Materials, 1989-1993 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Dowling, Kathryn, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Downer, Herb, circa 1970s (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Doyle, Gilian, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Drake, Donna, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Drake, Gillian, Undated (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Drake, Ronald, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Drake, Ronald, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Driver, Donald - Director, Status Quo Vadis at Arena Stage, 1971-1972 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - du Rand, Le Clanche, 1975-1976 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Dubois, Jeannette, Undated (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Duff-MacCormick, Cara, 1971-1972 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Duncanson, Tony, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - Dunfee, Nora, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Dunlap, Pamela, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 23)
      - Dunn, Augustine, 1972-1974 (Box 71, Folder 24)
      - Dutton, Nancy, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 25)
      - Duvall, Elizabeth, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 26)
      - Ebeling, George, 1965-1973 (Box 71, Folder 27)
      - Edegran, Lars, circa 1960s (Box 71, Folder 28)
      - Edwards, Beverly, Undated (Box 71, Folder 29)
      - Edwards, Charles, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Edwards, Ryan - Composer for Edith Stein, Undated (Box 71, Folder 31)
      - Eggleston, William, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 32)
      - Ehlers, Heather and Epstein, Millie, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 33)
      - Eigsti, Karl, 1960s - 1980s (Box 71, Folder 34)
      - Eikenberry, Jill, circa 1970s (Box 71, Folder 35)
      - Ekzarkhov, Vladimir, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 36)
      - Elcar, Dana, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 37)
      - Elice, Eric, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 38)
      - Elko, John, Undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Ellens, Rebecca, Undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Elliot, Marianna - Costume Designer, circa 1960s (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Emmanuel, Donna, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Emmons, Beverly, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Everly, Woody, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Engle, Morris, Undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Enten, Boni, 1972-1973 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Epps, Benjamin, 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Epstein, Pierre, 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Eric, David, 1974-1975 (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Ericson, Richard, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Escot, T.J., 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Estabrook, Christine, circa 1970s (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Estan, Hugh, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Esterman, Laura, Undated (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - Estes, Richard, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - Ehlers, Heather, circa 1980s (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Evans, David, 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 19)
      - Everett, Pamela, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - Everett, Tom, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 21)
      - Everhart, Kurt, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 22)
      - Ewer, Donald, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 23)
      - Eyermann, Jim, 1978-1980 (Box 72, Folder 24)
      - Executive Director's Files, 1950s - 1990s (Box 72, Folder 25)
      - Fairman, Michael, 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Farer, Ronnie, Undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Farley, J.J. and the Original Soul Stirrers, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Farr, Kimberly, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Farrell, Conchatta, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Feiner, Marjorie, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Felcher, Sarah, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Felder, Clarence, Undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Ferguson, Lou, Undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Fernandez, Jay, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Ferris, Geoffrey, Undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Fields, Robert, Undated (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Fignar, Jeff, Undated (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Fingerhut, Arden - Lighting Design, 1975-1985 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Finn, John, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Fisher, Linda, 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Fisher, Robert, circa 1980s (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Flacks, Niki, circa 1970s (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - Flaningham, Louisa, 1972-1973 (Box 73, Folder 19)
      - Flanagan, Pauline, 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - Flanagan, Walter, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Fleary, Dingwall, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 22)
      - Fletcher, Jay, 1968-1970 (Box 73, Folder 23)
      - Flood, Frank - Immigration Materials - Juno and the Paycock, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - Fong, Sandra Yen - Costume Designer, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 25)
      - Ford, Clebert, circa 1980s (Box 73, Folder 26)